[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 6 \u00d7 6) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "8",
        "10",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 6 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "52",
      "options": [
        "52",
        "53",
        "54",
        "51"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 6 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "55",
      "options": [
        "56",
        "55",
        "57",
        "54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 1 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "19",
        "17",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 9 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "8",
        "11",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 9 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "19",
        "18",
        "17",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 7 \u00d7 2) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "7",
        "10",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 4 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "11",
        "14",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 3 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "28",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "28",
        "29",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 10 \u00d7 4) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "9",
        "10",
        "11"
      ]
    }
]